Charles Korr's Major League Baseball Interview Audio Tapes 6355 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles Korr's Major League Baseball Interview Audio Tapes
1989-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Korr, Charles
6355 AV
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Interviews, audio cassette tapes.
Audio recordings of interviews conducted with baseball players, journalists, and labor executives by Charles Korr during his writing of The End of Baseball As We Knew It: The Players Union, 1960-1981 (University of Illinois Press, 2005).
8054802
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 29, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 05, 2014
Biographical / Historical
Charles Korr is Professor Emeritus at the University of Missouri--St. Louis.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5132m: Baseball Players Association Early Documents
Arrangement
Series 1: Broadcasters and Journalists, 1990-1991
Series 2: Former Major League Players, 1987-1992
Series 3: Officials and Employees of Major League Baseball and/or Clubs, 1989-1991
Series 4: Others, 1990
Bando, Sal; Barton, Bob; Bavasi, Buzzie; Boros, Steve; Bunning, Jim; Dalton, Harry; Cannon, Robert; Coleman, Joe; Downing, Al; Foley, Red; Gaherin, John; Hamilton, Steve; Hunter, Bob; Kauffman, Ewing; Kiner, Ralph; Koppett, Leonard; Korr, Charles; Marshall, Mike; Miller, Marvin; McCarver, Tim; McGuff, Joe; Pappas, Milt; Peters, Gary; Robertson, Oscar; Selig, Bud; Simmons, Ted; Smith, Reggie; Torre, Joe; White, Bill
8054802
- Series 1: Broadcasters and Journalists, 1990-1991
  - Bob Hunter, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    March 26, 1991.
  - Leonard Koppett, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    February 12, 1990.
  - Leonard Koppett, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Leonard Koppett, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Joe McGuff, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    November 16, 1990.
- Series 2: Former Major League Players, 1987-1992
  - Sal Bando, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    August 17, 1991.
  - Bob Barton, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    November 16, 1989.
  - Steve Boros, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Jim Bunning, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    June 30, 1987.
  - Al Downing, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Steve Hamilton, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    March 10, 1990.
  - Steve Hamilton, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Steve Hamilton, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ralph Kiner, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    November 15, 1989.
  - Mike Marshall, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    March 28, 1991.
  - Mike Marshall, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Tim McCarver, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    August 23, 1989.
  - Milt Pappas, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    June 29, 1987.
  - Gary Peters, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    March 27, 1991.
  - Ted Simmons, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    November 20, 1991.
  - Ted Simmons, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Reggie Smith, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Joe Torre, Joe Coleman, Red Foley, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    March 25, 1991. Tape includes interviews with broadcasters and journalists
  - Bill White, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    January 10, 1992.
- Series 3: Officials and Employees of Major League Baseball and/or Clubs, 1989-1991
  - Buzzie Bavasi, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    November 17, 1989.
  - Buzzie Bavasi, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Harry Dalton, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - John Gaherin, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - John Gaherin, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Ewing Kauffman, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Bud Selig, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Judge Robert Cannon, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    August 16, 1991.
  - Judge Robert Cannon, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Marvin Miller (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Marvin Miller (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Series 4: Others, 1990
  - Oscar Robertson, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    March 19, 1990.